Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
George Mason University: Public Relations Press Releases 1966-1989
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
GMU 004
36 boxes, 30 cubic feet
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open to research.
Biographical Historical Information
This collection covers the years 1966-1989.
Scope and Content Information
Collection contains printed press releases from GMU Public Relations (later University Relations) unit.
Arrangement
Arranged by date and Press release number.
Contents List
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - Student Applicants 1965 (Box Box 1)
  - Faculty Roster for 1965- 66 Academic Year (Box Box 1)
  - Library- Architect 02-12-65 (Box Box 1)
  - Staff Recruitment 1966 (Box Box 1)
  - No. Va. Cultural Planning Committee Meeting 01-03-67 (Box Box 1)
  - GMC Faculty Judges Science Fair 02-09-67 (Box Box 1)
  - No. Va. Governor's Conference on Education 03-02-67 (Box Box 1)
  - Rugby Match 03-09-67 (Box Box 1)
  - Delta Tau Sigma Dance 04-04-67 (Box Box 1)
  - Student Applicants 04-13-67 (Box Box 1)
  - Faculty Buffet Supper 05-18-67 (Box Box 1)
  - "George Mason College: For All The People?" 07-21-71 (Box Box 1)
  - Press Release: English Dept. Poetry/ Fiction Workshop 04-22-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Advisory: GMU Day, 1972- Advisory to Locals, T.V. (Box Box 1)
  - PHI MU Officer Installation 1972- Special to Springfield 4/4 other 4/7 (Box Box 1)
  - Alpha Chi Goes National (Quintillion Society) 04-14-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Transportation Conference (5/6 and 20) 04-14-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Special to Broadside: Cheerleader Clinic and Tryouts 04-12-72 (Box Box 1)
  - TEKE Public Service Weekend 04-26-72 (Box Box 1)
  - George Mason Day 04-14-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Holton Signs Separation Bill (and Picture) 04-07-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Commencement 05-16-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Chancellor Thompson's Statement on B. of V. Resolution Making Him Prexy GMU (Box Box 1)
  - Commencement 1972 06-03-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Consortium: Press Kit for Press Conference 06-27-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Fairfax High Lease Approved by Board 06-21-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Evening Session 07-14-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Summer Commencement 1972 (Box Box 1)
  - Commencement Aug. 1972 (John C. Wood) (Box Box 1)
  - Release Changes: GMU 08-04-72 (Box Box 1)
  - J. Gurfein GMU Appointment 06-14-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Student Consumer Report August 1972 (Box Box 1)
  - Lanfranco and Macdonald Named to All State Team (Box Box 1)
  - Resolution: Lorin A. Thompson Hall (Student Government 1972) (Box Box 1)
  - Board of Visitors Approves Consortium Participation (Box Box 1)
  - All State Soccer (Box box 1)
  - Basketball (Box Box 1)
  - Fencing 1972 (Box Box 1)
  - 8th District Congressional Debate (Box Box 1)
  - Physical Science Night (Box Box 1)
  - Willis, William- GMU Appointment (717172) (Box Box 1)
  - Advisory: Press Briefing- B. of V. Meeting Number 2 06-21-72 (Box Box 1)
  - Soccer: GMU VS. Hampden Sydney (Box Box 1)
  - Washington Area Collegiate Trap Shooting Championship (Box Box 1)
  - Cross Country (Box Box 1)
  - Soccer (Box Box 1)
  - Soccer: GMU as Old Dominion 1972 (Box Box 1)
  - Basketball: Catholic University and York (Pa.) (Box Box 1)
  - Press Release: Fall Semester 1972 "Back to School" 31STSPL872/ba (Box Box 1)
  - Hyman Feinstein (Box Box 1)
  - Country Music Release (Box Box 1)
  - Arms and the Man Release (Box Box 1)
  - Art Show Release (Box Box 1)
  - Guru Release (Box Box 1)
  - Governor's Conference: Sec. Brown (Box Box 1)
  - Governor's Conference: Sec. Miller Session (Box Box 1)
  - Governor's Conference: Sec. Rowe's Session (Box Box 1)
  - Governor's Conference: Sec. Whitham (Box Box 1)
  - Governor's Conference: Sec. Shiflet- Sec. Finance (Box Box 1)
  - General Gov. Conference (Box Box 1)
  - Conference and Workshop for State College and University Personal Directors (Box Box 1)
  - Pig Tournament (Box Box 1)
  - Abortion Panel Discussion (Box Box 1)
  - Forensics Win (Box Box 1)
  - Festival of the Arts Series of Releases (Box Box 1)
  - GMU Five Game Statistics (Box Box 1)
  - GMU Two-Game Statistics (Box Box 1)
  - Patriots Numerical Roster (Box Box 1)
  - Patriots VS Catholic University (Box Box 1)
  - GMU- Holiday Tournament (Box Box 1)
  - Virginia Austin Release (Box Box 1)
  - Women in Literature Release (Box Box 1)
  - Ground breaking Ceremonies (Box Box 1)
  - First Gear Concert (Box Box 1)
  - Women's Weightlifting (Box Box 1)
  - An Era of Excellence Concert (Box Box 1)
  - Writers Workshop Release (Box Box 1)
  - Spring Musical Events 1973 (Box Box 1)
  - Dr. Michael Kelley Release (Box Box 1)
  - TKE Installation of Officers (Box Box 1)
  - Student/Faculty Art Show (Box Box 1)
  - GMU vs. Roanoke and Bowie St. 1973 (Box Box)
  - Interim Graduation Release (Box Box 1)
  - GMU Chess Tournament (Box Box 1)
  - GMU Telescope Release (Box Box 1)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Discussion (Box Box 1)
  - Spring Play Release (Box Box 1)
  - Mary A. Marshall Release (Box Box 1)
  - Dance Recital (Box Box 1)
  - First Year Wrestling Team (Box Box 1)
  - Basketball Overview 1972-73 (Box Box 1)
  - Jorge Ponce Release (Box Box 1)
  - D.C. Institute of Chemistry Lecture (Box Box 1)
  - Presidential Announcement- Press Kit: Press Conference Dykstra (Box Box 1)
  - Radio Release: Press Release: Navy Band Concert (Box Box 1)
  - George Mason Day 1973 (Box Box 1)
  - PSA: International Night (Box Box 1)
  - Lorin Thompson: 1973 Graduation Address (Box Box 1)
  - 1973 Spring Graduation (Box Box 1)
  - President Thompson Retires (Box Box 1)
  - Summer Commencement 1973 Agronsky (Box Box 1)
  - PSA: Summer Courses 1973 (Box Box 2)
  - Business Dept.: Tax Aid to Poor (Box Box 2)
  - Agora Presentation: The Diary of Anne Frank (Box Box 2)
  - PSA: Black Awareness Week (Box Box 2)
  - Students to Pay Building Fee (Box Box 2)
  - Sex Education Film Festival (Box Box 2)
  - Black Arts Festival (Box Box 2)
  - American Studies Introduced (Box Box 2)
  - GMU Presidency Change- Over Thompson Turns Keys Over to Dykstra 1973 (Box Box 2)
  - Thompson's Retirement: Special to Charlottesville Progress (Box Box 2)
  - Basketball Clinic (Rudy Jones) Special to Prince George's Co. (Box Box 2)
  - Sundell: Dept. Chairman (English) (Box Box 2)
  - Invasion (Box Box 2)
  - Radio Release: Summer Graduation Agronsky- Speaker (Box Box 2)
  - Cohelan Appointment (Box Box 2)
  - Foreign Language Workshop (Box Box 2)
  - Hawkes Appointment- Snavely Appointment- Baxter Appointment (Box Box 2)
  - Grant: National Science Foundation (Box Box 2)
  - McConkey Appointment (Box Box 2)
  - Agronsky Speech (Box Box 2)
  - Giller House (Box Box 2)
  - Orchestra Formation (Box Box 2)
  - GMU 1973-74 Enrollment (Box Box 2)
  - PSA: Fall Registration 1973 (Box Box 2)
  - Master's Degree in English (Box Box 2)
  - Dr. Walls Named to National American Studies Faculty (Box Box 2)
  - Soder on Allende's Chile (Box Box 2)
  - East Asia (Box Box 2)
  - SEA Square Dance (Box Box 2)
  - Calendar of Events: SEA Sq. Dance (Box Box 2)
  - PSA: SEA Sq. Dance (Box Box 2)
  - Special: Forensics (Vienna) (Box Box 2)
  - Special: Forensics (Alex Hay.) (Box Box 2)
  - Special: Forensics (McLean) (Box Box 2)
  - Special: Forensics (Springfield) (Box Box 2)
  - Special: Forensics (Fairfax Falls) (Box Box 2)
  - Wilhelm Appointment (Box Box 2)
  - Germaine Bree: Visiting Scholar (Box Box 2)
  - East Asia Discussion (Box Box 2)
  - GMU Saxophone Recital (Box Box 2)
  - Derr (Box Box 2)
  - Play (Box Box 2)
  - Winter Commencement 1973 (Box Box 2)
  - Tax Seminar (Box Box 2)
  - Foreign Language Symposium (Box Box 2)
  - New Jersey Regional Forensics Win (Box Box 2)
  - Energy Crises (Box Box 2)
  - GMU Chamber Orchestra and Concert Band (Box Box 2)
  - Telescope (Box Box 2)
  - University Closing (Box Box 2)
  - Basketball Tourney (Newspapers) (Box Box 2)
  - Basketball Tourney (Radio and TV) (Box Box 2)
  - Basketball Preview (Box Box 2)
  - Forensics Team (Box Box 2)
  - Lowe Appointment (Box Box 2)
  - Commencement Preparation (Box Box 2)
  - Graduate Program Approval (Box Box 2)
  - Forensics Team Win (Box Box 2)
  - Investment Seminar (Box Box 2)
  - Arts and Crafts Day- Newspapers- Radio and TV (Box Box 2)
  - Vocational Exploration for Women- Newspaper (Box Box 2)
  - Arts Festival- Radio and TV- Newspaper (Box Box 2)
  - Andrew "Andy" Evans- Recruiter (Newspaper) (Box Box 2)
  - Forensics Tournament (Newspaper) (Box Box 2)
  - Application for Summer Session (Radio and TV) (Box Box 2)
  - Forensics Tourney (Radio and TV) (Box Box 2)
  - Movie Publicity (Box Box 2)
  - National Forensics League Tournament at GMU (Box Box 2)
  - Agora Society- Tryouts (Box Box 2)
  - Phi Mu Officers (Box Box 2)
  - Forensics (Box Box 2)
  - Mclean Phi Mu Officers (Box Box 2)
  - Alexandria Phi Mu Officer (1974) (Box Box 3)
  - Summer School (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics Tournament (Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics Tournament News Release Information Forms (Box Box 3)
  - Debate: Dick Williams- Old Dominion- Rod Low (Box Box 3)
  - Danish Gymnastic (Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics Tournament (Box Box 3)
  - Debate Tournament (Box Box 3)
  - Tuition- Faculty Salary Increase (Box Box 3)
  - Math Competition (Box Box 3)
  - Dr. Terrien Lecture (Box Box 3)
  - Arts and Crafts Day (Box Box 3)
  - Panel Discussion (Box Box 3)
  - Panel Discussion: Specials (Box Box 3)
  - Geography Morning (Box Box 3)
  - Chess Tourney (Box Box 3)
  - Women's Vocational Exploration Seminar Panel (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics Nationals (Box Box 3)
  - Women's Vocational Exploration (Radio) (Box Box 3)
  - Chess Tourney (Radio) (Box Box 3)
  - Geography Morning (Radio) (Box Box 3)
  - Elaine Peterson- Kathy Rowan (Forensics) (Box Box 3)
  - Story Schedule (Box Box 3)
  - Cinderella: Forensics (Box Box 3)
  - International Night (Box Box 3)
  - Monitor: Geography Morning (Box Box 3)
  - Nationals (Box Box 3)
  - Look Homeward Angel (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics (Box Box 3)
  - Pan Hellenic Scholarships: B. Bibb- C. Tyson (Box Box 3)
  - Women's Art Exhibit (Box Box 3)
  - Nationals- Mauren Brown (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics and Debate Radio Release (Box Box 3)
  - Debate Nationals- Pederson Schulin (Box Box 3)
  - Forensics Title (Box Box 3)
  - Concerts (Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Vice President (Box Box 3)
  - Women's Exhibit- D.C. Papers- Va. Papers (Box Box 3)
  - Debate Nationals (Box Box 3)
  - Appointments (Box Box 3)
  - Who's Who Award (Box Box 3)
  - Pederson- University Service Award (Box Box 3)
  - Jarrett University Service Award (Box Box 3)
  - Awards: Humphries and McCord (Box Box 3)
  - Chess- Radio- Newspaper (Box Box 3)
  - GEICO Awards (Box Box 3)
  - Student Union (Box Box 3)
  - TV- Forensics (Box Box 3)
  - Commencement (Box Box 3)
  - Commencement- Media Advisory- Radio and Tv- Psychology- (Box Box 3)
  - Key Mussell (Box Box 3)
  - Commencement- Sarah McClendon's Speech, Spring 19974 (Box Box 3)
  - Off- Campus Courses (Newspaper and Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Chorus (Newspaper and Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Chess Result (Box Box 3)
  - Physics- Dr. Papaconstantopoulos (Box Box 3)
  - Bicentennial (Newspaper and Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Burt Appointment (Box Box 3)
  - VP. Titles (Box Box 3)
  - Burt Sidebar (Box Box 3)
  - Falls Church Faculty (Box Box 3)
  - Sennott Promotion (Box Box 3)
  - Alexandria Faculty- Annandale Faculty- Springfield Faculty (Box Box 3)
  - Bergoffen Promotions (Box Box 3)
  - Fairfax Faculty Promotions (Box Box 3)
  - 24 Faculty Promotions (Box Box 3)
  - Alexandria Faculty (Box Box 3)
  - GMU Concert (Newspaper and Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - Non-Credit Courses (Radio and TV) (Box Box 3)
  - COIT Visit- Newspapers- Radio and TV (Box Box 3)
  - Special Education (Box Box 3)
  - Jobs and Housing- Newspaper- Radio and TV (Box Box 3)
  - Rawls Appointment (Box Box 3)
  - Commencement- Newspapers- Radio and TV (Box Box 3)
  - Evening Session- Newspapers- Radio and TV (Box Box 3)
  - Circus Kingdom (Box Box 3)
  - GMU Commencement (Box Box 3)
  - Off- Campus Courses (Box Box 3)
  - Off- Campus Courses 1974 (Box Box 4)
  - Enrollment (Box Box 4)
  - Agora: "The Beggars Opera" (Box Box 4)
  - Ensembles (Box Box 4)
  - Non- Credit Courses (Potpourii) (Box Box 4)
  - Auditions For Ensembles (Box Box 4)
  - Adult Student (Box Box 4)
  - 1974 Debate Workshop (Box Box 4)
  - New Asistant Coach (Box Box 4)
  - New Faculty Members (Box Box 4)
  - Forensics (Box Box 4)
  - Law School Report (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. Joseph Kanyon Clarinet Recital (Box Box 4)
  - Career Day (Box Box 4)
  - Chorus Concert (Radio and TV) (Box Box 4)
  - Kanyon Concert (Box Box 4)
  - Collegium Musicum (Box Box 4)
  - Susan Frye Clarinetist (Box Box 4)
  - McConkey- Woman of the Year (Box Box 4)
  - Annandale Faculty- Alexandria Faculty- Vienna Faculty- Maryland Faculty- Falls Church Faculty (Box Box 4)
  - Forensics- Maddox- Arlington (Box Box 4)
  - Faculty Appointments (Box Box 4)
  - Agora: "The Beggars Opera" (Box Box 4)
  - Construction of Three Story Flag By Veterans Club (Box Box 4)
  - American Heritage Week (Box Box 4)
  - Recruitment of Black Students to GMU By Andrew Evans (Box Box 4)
  - November 14 Student Recital (Radio and Newspaper) (Box Box 4)
  - Invitational Debate Tournament (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. Trub- New Chair of Bio Dept. (Box Box 4)
  - The Fantastics (Newspapers and Radio) (Box Box 4)
  - Diatribe for Jazz Ensemble (Newspapers and Radio) (Box Box 4)
  - Spring Courses Available (Box Box 4)
  - Evening Undergraduate Registration By Mail (Box Box 4)
  - Laboratory Demonstration Technical Course Offered (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. Ring (Box Box 4)
  - Cornelsen Memorial (Box Box 4)
  - Scholarships Awards in Biology (Box Box 4)
  - Dedication Ceremony of Cornelsen on December 4 (Box Box 4)
  - 5000 Dollar Grant to History Department (Box Box 4)
  - GMU Chorus Concert (Newspapers) (Box Box 4)
  - GMU Chorus X-Mas Concert (Radio) (Box Box 4)
  - Diane Smith (Box Box 4)
  - Constitution History Course (Box Box 4)
  - Education Conference (Box Box 4)
  - Housing (Box Box 4)
  - Forensic Team- Towson (Box Box 4)
  - New Graduate Courses (Radio and Newspapers) (Box Box 4)
  - Non- Credit Courses (Radio and Newspapers) (Box Box 4)
  - Federal Theatre Project (Newspaper) (Box Box 4)
  - Winter Commencement- Will Speaks (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. Greer's Grant (Box Box 4)
  - Who's Who- Alexandria- Vienna- McLean- Journal and Globe (Box Box 4)
  - Act II and You (Box Box 4)
  - Winter Commencement Geo Will (Box Box 4)
  - Who's Who in Springfield (Box Box 4)
  - Festival of Exposure (Box Box 4)
  - Master Class Piano (Box Box 4)
  - Scholarship- Rocky Run Garden Club (Box Box 4)
  - Milton Barnes Papers (Box Box 4)
  - Festival of Exposure (Box Box 4)
  - Epler Lecture (Box Box 4)
  - Bond to Speak at Festival of Exposure (Box box 4)
  - GMU Sweeps New Jersey Forensics Tournament (Box Box 4)
  - Bicentennial Bureau Established (Box Box 4)
  - Don Nash- Dean of Students (Box Box 4)
  - Dr. Abernathy Lecture (Box Box 4)
  - Folger Fellowship Awarded (Box Box 4)
  - GMU Admissions Office Extends Hours (2-75/ 12-75) (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Summer Session Catalog Now Available (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Agora Society Produces "I Remember Mama" (Box Box 5)
  - Concert By Kanyon: Mar. 10 (Box Box 5)
  - Julian Bond Speaks at GMU (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Students Honored at Band Festival (Box Box 5)
  - GMU President to Visit Red China (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Sponsors TV Series on Transportation Problems (Box Box 5)
  - GMU's Festival of Arts Begins With Music (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Holds Workshop on Aging (Box Box 5)
  - The University and the Older Citizen (Box Box 5)
  - Dr. Burt Book Presented (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Meets With City and County Planners (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Hosts Forensics Tourney (Box Box 5)
  - The Festival of the Arts (Box Box 5)
  - Fraternity Sponsors Run for Children's Hospital (Box Box 5)
  - Dance Notation Lecture (Box Box 5)
  - Sampson of Ethiopia (Box Box 5)
  - Lindsey Lecture (Box Box 5)
  - Sampson of Ethiopia (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Sweeps Home Tourney (Box Box 5)
  - GMU to Hold Admissions Transfer Conference (Box Box 5)
  - GMU- Faculty Member Receives Grant to Compose (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Will Host Public Relations Community Workshop (Box Box 5)
  - Teaching English As a Second Language (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Professor Receives Folger Fellowship (Box Box 5)
  - Bluegrass Festival (Newspapers and Radio) (Box Box 5)
  - Audubon Lecture to be Given at GMU (Newspaper) (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Holds Chess Tourney (Newspaper and Radio) (Box Box 5)
  - Audubon Lecture (Box Box 5)
  - Visiting Scholars Lecture at GMU (Box Box 5)
  - Who Killed John F. Kennedy (Radio and Newspaper) (Box Box 5)
  - Chemicals in Food Lecture at GMU (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Professor to Attend Artist's Retreat (Box Box 5)
  - GMU to Compete in National Forensics Tourney (Box Box 5)
  - Vijaya Prabhakar Concert (Box Box 5)
  - GMU to Present Dance Alliance (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Hosts International Night (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Professor Receives NEH Grant (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Chamber Orchestra and Symphonic Winds Perform in Concert (Radio and Newspaper) (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Plans On-Campus Health Service (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Board Approves Housing Plan (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Memorial Fund Established in Honor of George Moseley (Box Box 5)
  - Chess Tourney For Students Grade 1-16 (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Places 11th in Forensics Tournament (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Elects First Black Woman as S.G. President (Box Box 5)
  - Concert By GMU Chorus and the Collegium Musicum (Box Box 5)
  - Five GMU Seniors Receive Geico Award (Box Box 5)
  - GMU President Highlights China Trip (Box Box 5)
  - VP of American Council on Education to be GMU Commencement (Box Box 5)
  - GMU Chamber Orchestra and Symphonic Winds Concert (Box Box 5)
  - Radford Concert Band to Perform at GMU (Box Box 5)
  - Commencement Releases (Box Box 5)
  - John Kelly- Leisure Research (Box Box 5)
  - Off Campus History Course (Box Box 5)
  - Summer Chorus Course Offering (Box Box 5)
  - Dr. Wilbert King Grant (Box Box 5)
  - Kominars Named President of Performing Arts Soc. of Alex (Box Box 5)
  - Barnes Exhibit Opening (Box Box 5)
  - Summer Commencement (Box Box 5)
  - Summer Chorus Concert (Box Box 5)
  - Juana Rosa Pita (Box Box 5)
  - Fox's Summer Graduation Speech Picture of President Dykstra at Graduation (Box Box 5)
  - Housing (Box Box 5)
  - Student Jobs (Box Box 5)
  - Alcohol Problems (Box Box 5)
  - Atlantic Economic (Box Box 5)
  - Piano Recital (Box Box 5)
  - Performing Groups (Box Box 5)
  - Film Festival (Box Box 5)
  - Finley Presentation (Box Box 5)
  - Panhellenic Scholarship (Box Box 5)
  - Godwin Visit (Box Box 5)
  - Political Forum (Box Box 5)
  - Minority Affairs Seminar Release (Box Box 5)
  - Fall 1975 Concert (Box Box 5)
  - Talent Show (Box Box 5)
  - Dr. Sam di Bonaventura (Box Box 5)
  - Publicity on Play Production "Grease" (Box Box 5)
  - Hunting Lecture (Box Box 5)
  - Minority Affairs and Seminar (Box Box 5)
  - Foreign Language Symposium (Box Box 5)
  - Mash AAVA (Box Box 5)
  - Education 500 (Box Box 5)
  - Econ Dinner/ Congressman Fisher (Box Box 5)
  - Children's Lit (Box Box 5)
  - Women's Club (Box Box 5)
  - Bicentennial Campus (Box Box 5)
  - Chamber Orchestra (Box Box 5)
  - Berrigan (Box Box 5)
  - Chemistry 500 (Box Box 5)
  - Winter Graduation (Box Box 6)
  - Sports Information Director (12-75/ 12-76) (Box Box 6)
  - Commencement Winter (Box Box 6)
  - Who's Who 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - Charles and Polly Webber (Scottish Rite) (Box Box 6)
  - Symphonic Workshop (Box Box 6)
  - Black Festival (Box Box 6)
  - Dr. Shaffer MOTH (Box Box 6)
  - Food Additives Lecture (Box Box 6)
  - Chamber Orchestra Symphonic Winds (Box Box 6)
  - Stephen Barton (Box Box 6)
  - Dr. Wall's Sea Grant (Box Box 6)
  - Chorus- Italy (Box Box 6)
  - Alpha Chi Library (Box Box 6)
  - Sacpino (Box Box 6)
  - Nurse Consciousness Day (Box Box 6)
  - Jazz Ensemble (Box Box 6)
  - GMU Establishes Bicentennial Bureau (Box Box 6)
  - Faculty Art Show (Box Box 6)
  - Ashtor Heights Scholarship (Box Box 6)
  - Houlgate Fellowship (Box Box 6)
  - Health Fair (Box Box 6)
  - Summer Session (Box Box 6)
  - Spring Concert: Chamber Orchestra- Symphonic Winds (Box Box 6)
  - ARA Civil War Exhibit (Box Box 6)
  - Forensics Team: Tournament (Box Box 6)
  - Icland Study Tour (Box Box 6)
  - Srinivasan Fellowship (Box Box 6)
  - VAS- VJAS Meeting (Box Box 6)
  - Management Seminar and Photo (Box Box 6)
  - Spring Commencement (Box Box 6)
  - 4th Annual GMU Chess Tour (Box Box 6)
  - Forensics/ Nat'l/ Photo (Box Box 6)
  - Telescope/ Cardinal (Box Box 6)
  - Foreign Film Disc/ PSA (Box Box 6)
  - FTP- NEH Grant (Box Box 6)
  - VJAS Winners 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - VAS- Honorary Life Members 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - VAS- Fellows 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - VJAS- Awards with Pictures (Box Box 6)
  - Commencement Ceremonies Spring 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - VAS- Lewis Harsley Awards (Box Box 6)
  - GMUSTB With Calendare (Box Box 6)
  - Language Heritage Institute (Box Box 6)
  - New Degree Programs (Box Box 6)
  - Law Related Education Institute (Box Box 6)
  - GMU Tutorial Service and Public Service Announce (Box Box 6)
  - Summer Chorus (Box Box 6)
  - Psychological Clinic (Box Box 6)
  - Crawford Grant (Box Box 6)
  - Expanded Tutorial Service (Box Box 6)
  - Special Ed/ Given Grant (Box Box 6)
  - Off- Campus Student House Request (Box Box 6)
  - U.S. Chess Open (Box Box 6)
  - S. C. Dawson III: GMU Descendent (Box Box 6)
  - PSA.NR Summer Chorus 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - 1976 Summer Commencement (Box Box 6)
  - PSA- 15 Seconds: U.S. Chess Open- 30 Seconds: U.S. Chess Open (Box Box 6)
  - Calendar Item: Chess Open, Folder 59 (Box Box 6)
  - GMU/ NOVA English Composition: Class at Manassas (Box Box 6)
  - TV Equipment Grant (Box Box 6)
  - Women in Science Grant (Box Box 6)
  - First Annual Patriot Golf Tourney for Sports Foundation (Box Box 6)
  - Summer Grad Featurettes (Box Box 6)
  - Off- Campus English 310 (Extended Studies) (Box Box 6)
  - Memo: Chess Open Celebrities (Box Box 6)
  - Chess: First Round- Biyiasas Buckley W/Photo (Box Box 6)
  - Chess: Bisguier Simultaneous W/ Photo (Box Box 6)
  - 1976- 1977 Invitation to Participate and Practice Schedule (Box Box 6)
  - Summer Education Institutes (Box Box 6)
  - Memo: Living Chess (Box Box 6)
  - Grad Course: Civil War (Taught in Manassas) (Box Box 6)
  - Food Additives (Box Box 6)
  - Memo: Awards Kavalek Simultaneous Chess (Box Box 6)
  - Chess Wrap-Up With Catline (Box Box 6)
  - McConkey Appointment to CAS Associate Dean (Box Box 6)
  - Shakespeare (Box Box 6)
  - National Symphony Chamber Orchestra (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: Potpourri (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: National Symphony Chamber Orchestra (Box Box 6)
  - Board of Visitors Election (Box Box 6)
  - John C. Evans- Assistant Dean of the Graduate School at GMU (Box Box 6)
  - Barbara Spath: BIS Coordinator (Box Box 6)
  - Pre- Primary Education Committee (Robert Gilstrap) (Box Box 6)
  - Hecht Lecture: Soviet Life (Box Box 6)
  - Textbooks: Resources Center (Box Box 6)
  - Tutorial: Special to Six Area Newsletters (Box Box 6)
  - Raper Book Collection (Box Box 6)
  - Washington Channel Jazz Band (Box Box 6)
  - PSA Food Additives (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: "Little Mary" (30 Sec.)- "Little Mary" (60 Sec.) (Box Box 6)
  - Little Mary Sunshine (Box Box 6)
  - Food Additives (Box Box 6)
  - Career Seminars (Box Box 6)
  - Counseling Center Programs (Box Box 6)
  - Atlantic Economic Conference (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: Reformation Music Concert (Box Box 6)
  - 100 Record Gift to Fine and Performing Arts Department (Box Box 6)
  - PSA: Sex Education Symposium (Box Box 6)
  - Children's Book Week (Box Box 6)
  - Parent- Infant Education Program (Box Box 6)
  - Kabuki Theatre Workshop (Box Box 6)
  - Music Audition Dates (Box Box 6)